hankypanky.com 2014-10-17

# Privacy Policy on HankyPanky.com!

HANKY PANKY PRIVACY POLICY: (last modified May, 2013) 

Hanky Panky Ltd. (“Hanky Panky”) understands that our users of www.hankypanky.com are concerned about how personal information is collected and used. Please be assured that we take privacy very seriously and are committed to safeguarding personal information. This notice describes our Privacy Policy, which covers the personal information that we collect on our website. By accessing and using our website, you are agreeing to be legally bound by this Privacy Policy. The Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. You should check the date of the policy and review any changes since the last version. 

We may collect personal information from you, including your name, email address, postal address, phone number, credit card number, gender, birthday, personal interests, etc., when you visit our website and/or place an order online or by phone, save your information with us online, register with us, contact us with a question or concern, or participate in a contest, promotion, or survey. We maintain a record of your product interests and the purchases you make online or by phone. We may combine all of this information with information about you that we acquire from our joint marketing partners, from unrelated third parties, and from our other brands, if any. We also collect and store the Internet Protocol (“IP”) addresses of individuals that visit our site. An IP address provides general statistical information, such as browsing activity, areas of greatest interest on the site, general demographic information and other basic information that we will use for system administration. If you use our "email this style to a friend" or otherwise share from our site to a friend, we will also collect your friend's name and email address. Your friend’s information is only used to send the forwarding email and is not saved in our customer or marketing databases. 

Hanky Panky collects various types of personal information about you both online and offline, as described in this privacy policy. Under California law, customers of Hanky Panky who are residents of California may request certain information about our disclosure of personal information during the prior calendar year to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write to us at the following address:   
Hanky Panky Ltd.   
Customer Relations   
373 Park Avenue South – 12th floor   
New York, NY 10016   
Alternatively, you may send us an email at contact-us@hankypanky.com with the words "California Privacy Rights" in the subject line. 

Hanky Panky is determined to protect your privacy. We only collect information in an effort to improve your shopping experience and that allows us to communicate with you about our products, services, contests and promotions. We may use your personal information in the following ways:   
\- To process and fulfill your order, including to send you emails to confirm your order status and shipment   
\- To communicate with you and to send you information by email, postal mail, telephone, text message, or other means about our products, services, contests, and promotions, unless you have directed us not to contact you with promotional communications   
\- To administer and fulfill our contests and other promotions   
\- To help us learn more about your shopping preferences   
\- To help us address problems with and improve our site design, products and services   
\- To enhance your shopping experience   
\- To analyze trends and statistics   
\- To protect the security or integrity of our websites and our business   
\- To contact you if necessary   
We only use aggregate audience details (where no individual is identifiable) to help us improve our understanding of our users and their preferences. We only share specific information with third parties that provide services on our behalf or with whom we have partnered to offer a particular product or service. For example, we provide relevant shipping information to UPS, our shipping partner, so that they may deliver your order.   
Signing up for our e-mail list allows you to receive promotional materials from Hanky Panky. Each e-mail you receive will give you the option to unsubscribe. We do not share our e-mail list with any third parties. We may have to release information (which could include contents of e-mail communications between any persons) in the unlikely event of a legal requirement on us or pursuant to a court order. In addition, we may divulge personal information if we or any of our service providers or consultants believe that such disclosure is necessary to address any unlawful acts or acts that may endanger the health or safety of another customers or of the general public.   
When you place an order on any of our website, we use this information to process and track your order and contact you via email, postal mail or phone if we have any questions or concerns regarding your order. If you provide an email address during checkout, you will also receive order confirmation and shipping status emails.   
We also maintain a record of your purchases made on our website.   
We may also share your information, including, without limitation, your email address (but not your credit card information) with unaffiliated third parties that would enable them to contact you about products or services you may be interested in.   
In the unlikely event of a sale of some or all of our business, Hanky Panky may disclose your personal information to a purchaser that agrees to abide by the terms and conditions of this privacy policy. 

**_Customized advertising (behavioral marketing)_**

Advertisements displayed to you on our websites and elsewhere on the Web may be customized to your interests and preferences, based on information learned about you as you use our websites and the Web in general. If you do not want to participate in this, please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp to opt-out. 

**_Marketing email communications_**

At various points on our website, you have the option to join our email list and receive information about our products, services and offers. Also, if you provide us with your email address when you register online or update your account, log-in, place an order, make a customer service inquiry, opt-in to receive our emails, shop online, request a catalog, participate in a sweepstakes, contest, promotion or survey, or buy a Hanky Panky gift card, you may automatically be added to our email list and receive marketing or promotional information from us. 

If you do not wish to receive Hanky Panky marketing emails, you may opt-out by clicking on the unsubscribe link found at the bottom of all Hanky Panky marketing emails, or by emailing contact-us@hankypanky.com with the following: 

• The phrase " no Hanky Panky emailOpt-Out" in the subject line   
• Your name and email address 

From time to time, we may share your information, including, without limitation, email addresses (but not your credit card information), with unaffiliated third parties whose products or services may be of interest to you and who have their own privacy policy in place. 

If you do not wish to receive marketing emails from these third parties, you may opt-out by emailing customer service at 

• The phrase "do not share email" in the subject line   
• Your name and email address 

You can also contact us via postal mail regarding any of the above by writing to: 

Hanky Panky Ltd.   
Customer Relations   
373 Park Avenue South – 12th floor   
New York, NY 10016 

Or you may contact us by phone at 877.447.4811, 24 hours a day, seven days a week. Please be aware that it can take up to 10 business days to remove you from our marketing email lists. And although we will no longer share your contact information with unaffiliated third parties for their marketing purposes, if they already have your information you will have to opt-out of their marketing communications by contacting them directly. If you opt-out from receiving our marketing emails, you will continue to receive order confirmation and shipping status emails. 

Our website may contain links to sites other than our own. Those sites may have their own privacy policies. Neither we nor any of our service providers have any responsibility for those sites and we provide these links solely for the convenience of our visitors. We encourage you to review the privacy policies and terms of use of any third-party sites or services before providing any of them with any of your personal information. 

Hanky Panky is concerned about the privacy of young children and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from a child under 13. We do not sell products for purchase by children and any children's products we sell are for purchase by adults only. Our website is not directed at children under 13 and does not knowingly collect any personal information from children under 13. 

**_Use of Cookies, Pixel Tags/Clear GIFs/Web Beacons_**

A cookie is a small data file that websites often store on your hard drive. A cookie may contain information (such as unique user ID), which is used to track the pages of the sites you’ve visited. Hanky Panky uses cookies to preserve the contents of your shopping bag between your visits as well as to measure activity on the site which allows us to determine which areas and features of the site are most popular.  Also, third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on your past visits to our websites.  ( _See_ "Customized advertising (behavioral marketing)" above.)  You can set your browser to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you turn off cookies or refuse them, though, you will not be able to make a purchase from the site, nor will we be able to recognize you as a registered user to allow you access to your account information.   
A pixel tag, also known as a clear GIF or web beacon, is an invisible tag placed on certain pages of our site but not on your computer. When you access these pages, pixel tags generate a generic notice of that visit. They usually work in conjunction with cookies, registering when a particular computer visits a particular page. If you turn off cookies the pixel tag will simply detect an anonymous website visit. 

**_Notice to P3P Users_**

The Platform for Privacy Preferences Project (P3P) is a standard developed by the World Wide Web Consortium (W3W) that provides an automated, machine-readable mechanism for understanding the use of your Personal Information by the websites you visit. P3P uses a standardized set of multiple choice questions covering the major elements of a website’s privacy policy to provide a cross-section of how the particular website handles the personally identifiable information of its users. P3P-enabled browsers can automatically read this set of preferences made available by P3P-enabled websites and compare this information to the user’s own set of privacy preferences. 

Protecting your order information is a priority for us. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect the security of your online order information. 

**_Accessing our web site from outside the U.S._**   

If you are visiting hankypanky.com from a location outside the United States, you will be connected through and to servers located within the United States. We currently accept online orders only from customers in the United States. By providing your information to us, you agree that all personal information will be used in accordance with this privacy policy and pursuant to U.S. law. 

We may update our privacy policy from time to time. Whenever we make a change, we will post the updated policy at this site and we encourage you to check our policy periodically. If we make a material change to our privacy policy that would lessen your privacy rights, we will either continue to honor our prior policy for information that we collected when it was in force, or we will ask for your consent to the change. If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy, please contact us: 

• By email: contact-us@hankypanky.com   
• By phone: 1.877.447.4811, Monday-Friday from 9 a.m. to 6 p.m EST   
• By mail: Hanky Panky Ltd.   
373 Park Avenue South – 12th floor   
New York, NY 10016 

In no event shall Hanky Panky or any of their affiliated entities or suppliers be liable for any indirect, special, punitive, incidental, exemplary or consequential damages even if these entities have been previously advised of the possibility of such damages, whether in an action, under contract, negligence or any other theory, arising out of or in connection with the use, inability to use or performance of the information, services, products and materials available from the site. These limitations shall apply not withstanding any failure of essential purpose or the existence of any limited remedy. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on how long an implied warranty lasts, or the exclusion or limitation of liability for consequential or incidental damages, the above limitations may not apply to you. 

No transaction of data over the internet is guaranteed to be completely secure. It may be possible for third parties not under the control of Hanky Panky to intercept or access transmissions or private communications unlawfully. While we strive to protect your personal information, neither Hanky Panky nor any of our service providers can ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us over the internet. Any such transmission is done at your own risk. 

Please address any questions regarding our Privacy Policy or our practices concerning Personal Information by writing to: 

Hanky Panky Ltd.   
373 Park Avenue South -12th floor   
New York, NY 10016   
Attn: Privacy Officer 

Please include information in your communication to us that will help us identify your account so we can assist you with your inquiry or request. 

The laws of the State of New York will govern this Privacy Policy without giving effect to any principles of conflict of law.
